Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Returning Pearl)
Lord Jing.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Yuan, you are here.
I thought you'd never step foot into Kunning Palace again.
Your Majesty,
The situation along the Burmese border is growing tense.
His Majesty mobilized troops to quell the unrest.
I was busy with official matters
so I couldn't visit Your Majesty.
Please forgive me
for being rude.
Yuan, you've grown up.
You have your mother's eyes.
This is...
When you were a child,
you were envious of the other princes because they had pouches
sewn by their mothers.
I knew that
but I only wanted you to study hard
and failed to realize the importance of a pouch sewn by your mother.
Now, I finally have time.
However,
I don't know if you still need it, Yuan.
I need it.
This is
the most exquisite pouch I've ever seen.
I'm unfilial.
You raised me up
and educated me
but I have to leave before I can repay you
for raising me.
You're leaving?
I'm sure you are leaving with Lin Er.
It's fine if you've thought it through.
I will not trouble you again.
Your Majesty,
this has nothing to do with Lin Er.
It's because I...
There's no need to explain, Yuan.
I've thought it through during this period.
I will leave matters of the rear palace
and devote to Buddhism.
Consort Ling
will take care of His Majesty.
I can rest assured.
As for you,
you've already
reached an age where you can decide for yourself.
Go on.
The only thing I can do
is to pray for blessings for you.
Your Majesty,
this is the jade pendant
Mother left behind when I was young.
Whenever I see it,
it feels like my mother is still by my side.
I'm giving it to you now.
If you miss me,
just look at it
and think of it
as my mother and me are still by your side.
From now on,
with distances so vast and days so long,
who knows when we will meet again?
But no matter where I am,
I hope Your Majesty
can have a pure heart
and a healthy body.
I will
bid farewell now.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I remember
everything you told me.
However,
I can't give you cakes, coffee, and ice cream.
So, I...
I have no regrets
about having you love me like this.
After drinking this cross-cupped wine,
I will be yours.
Sui Sui.
It'll be the hour of Zi soon.
I should leave.
Jing Yuan, don't go.
I don't want you to leave.
Go back.
Go back to your own world.
Remember.
You once had someone called Jing Yuan
who was willing to live with you forever.
(Lin, it's the hour of Zi. Leave immediately.)
(Otherwise, you'll also vanish forever.)
I...
I've returned.
Sui Sui.
- Sui Sui. - Sui Sui, how are you?
Sui Sui, how are you?
Are you feeling better?
- Sui Sui, are you all right? - Do you feel unwell?
You scared me when the light fell.
Sui Sui, are you all right?
The set is ready
and the script has been amended according to our request.
Do you think
you can still continue?
If you still feel unwell, let's not force it.
- Can you do it? - Yes.
- I'm fine. - Are you all right?
Let's go.
I've made everyone wait.
I'm fine.
Slow down.